<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faqs>
    <faq>
        <question>What are the peak hours for booking a badminton court?</question>
        <answer>Peak hours vary depending on location and demand. Generally, evenings and weekends tend to be the busiest times. We recommend booking in advance to secure your preferred time slot.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Can I book multiple courts for a tournament or event?</question>
        <answer>Yes, you can book multiple courts for tournaments or events. Please just reserve your slot via scheduling page.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Can I modify my reservation after it's been confirmed?</question>
        <answer>Yes, you can modify your reservation, such as changing the time or duration, as long as there is availability.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>What happens if I need to cancel my reservation?</question>
        <answer>If you need to cancel your reservation, please do so at least 24 hours in advance. Failure to cancel within the specified time may result in a cancellation fee.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Is there a minimum age requirement to book a badminton court?</question>
        <answer>Yes, players must be at least 18 years old to book a court. However, players under 18 can play if accompanied by an adult who made the reservation.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Can I bring my own equipment, like rackets and shuttlecocks, or are they provided?</question>
        <answer>We encourage players to bring their own equipment, including rackets and shuttlecocks. However, if needed, equipment rental options may be available at the facility.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Are there any specific dress code requirements for playing badminton?</question>
        <answer>While there's no strict dress code, we recommend wearing comfortable athletic attire and non-marking shoes to ensure safety and agility on the court.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Can I invite guests who are not playing to watch the games?</question>
        <answer>Absolutely! Spectators are welcome to watch the games from designated viewing areas within the facility. Please ensure they adhere to any facility rules and regulations.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Are there any restrictions on food and drinks inside the badminton facility?</question>
        <answer>To maintain cleanliness and safety, some facilities may have restrictions on outside food and drinks. However, many facilities have a designated area for refreshments or may have a cafe on-site where you can purchase snacks and beverages.</answer>
    </faq>
    <faq>
        <question>Are there any specific rules or regulations regarding behavior on the badminton courts?</question>
        <answer>Yes, to ensure a safe and enjoyable experience for all players, certain rules and regulations regarding behavior on the courts may apply. This includes respecting opponents, following facility guidelines, and adhering to fair play principles.</answer>
    </faq>
</faqs>
